Guide to the Duke Gardens Foundation records, 1912-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Financial Records, 1958-1993 (Box 126)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - S, 1963 (1 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - S, 1963 (2 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Somerset Plumbing Supply, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Somerset Rose Nursery, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - T, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - U-V, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - W, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - X, Y, Z, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Petty Cash, 1964 (1 of 3) (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Petty Cash, 1964 (2 of 3) (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Petty Cash, 1964 (3 of 3) (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Duke Farms to Duke Gardens Foundation - Labor & Material Expenses, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Duke Sales, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - A, 1964 (1 of 2) (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - A, 1964 (2 of 2) (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Aneskewich, Edward P., 1964 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Arcade Propane Gas, Inc., 1964 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - B, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Berman & Company, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Brewer, Elmer, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Burns, W.J. International Detective Agency, Inc., 1964 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - C, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Cooperative GLF Exchange, Inc., 1964 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - D, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Deluccia, Frank, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - E, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - F, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - G, 1964 (1 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - G, 1964 (2 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - H, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - H & E-lectric Co., 1964 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Houser Auto Supply, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - I, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - J, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - K, 1964 (1 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - K, 1964 (2 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - L, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - M, 1964 (1 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - M, 1964 (2 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Manpower, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - N, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - NJ Bell Telephone Inc., 1964 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - O, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - P, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Pepsi Cola Metropolitan Bottling Co., 1964 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - R, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Cooperative GLF Service Inc., 1964 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Hardware Co., 1964 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Plumbing Supply Co., 1964 (1 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Plumbing Supply Co., 1964 (2 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Russell, Gerald S., 1964 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - S, 1964 (1 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - S, 1964 (2 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Somerset Plumbing Supply, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Somerville Electrical Supply Co., 1964 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Somerville Hardware Co., 1964 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - T, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - U, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - V, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - W, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - X, Y, Z, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Cashbook, Journal & General Ledger, 1959–1965 (1 of 3) (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Cashbook, Journal & General Ledger, 1959–1965 (2 of 3) (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Cashbook, Journal & General Ledger, 1959–1965 (3 of 3) (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Reports on Duke Gardens Foundation, 1959-1966 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and cash disbursements, 1963 (1 of 2) (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and cash disbursements, 1963 (2 of 2) (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - DGF Requisition Invoices, 1964 Jul 21-Oct 16 (1 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - DGF Requisition Invoices, 1964 Jul 21-Oct 16 (2 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - General Ledger, 1965 (1 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger, 1965 (2 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Dividends, 1966-1968, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - General Ledger and Journal Book, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation IRS Forms 990 PF/990 AR, 1970-1980 (1 of 3) (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation IRS Forms 990 PF/990 AR, 1970-1980 (2 of 3) (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation IRS Forms 990 PF/990 AR, 1970-1980 (3 of 3) (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Real Estate Taxes, Application for Exemption, 1970-1991 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation State of Delaware Franchise Tax Reports, 1970-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation State of Delaware Franchise Tax Reports, 1970-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - General Ledger and Journal Book, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - General Ledger and Journal Book, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - General Ledger, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - General Ledger, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Financial Statements, 1974-1990 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - General Ledger, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - General Ledger, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation IRS Forms 941, 1976-1989 (1 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation IRS Forms 941, 1976-1989 (2 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation IRS Forms 941, 1976-1989 (3 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger and General Journal, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - General Journal and General Ledger, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Tax Returns - Form 990, 1978-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Tax Returns - Form 990, 1978-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - General Journal and General Ledger, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - General Journal and General Ledger, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - General Journal and General Ledger, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation IRS Forms 990 PF/990 AR, 1981-1989 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - General Journal and General Ledger, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Journal-Ledger, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Tax Refund, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Journal-Ledger, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Journal-Ledger, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - General Ledger, 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger, 1986 (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - General Ledger, 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - General Ledger, 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - General Ledger, 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - General Ledger, 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - General Ledger, 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger, 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - General Ledger, 1991 (1 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - General Ledger, 1991 (2 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - General Ledger, 1991 (3 of 3) (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Total Expenses, 1993-1995 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Statement of Income, 1993-1996 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Bills for transporting plant material from DGF to Rough Point, 1997-1998 (1 of 2) (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Bills for transporting plant material from DGF to Rough Point, 1997-1998 (2 of 2) (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda regarding Cymbidium orchids at Duke Gardens, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Blank Gift Certificate for a tour of Duke Gardens, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Farm Sales, 1958–1963 Jan (Oversize-box 86, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1965–1966 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 86, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1965–1966 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 86, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1967–1968 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box 87, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1967–1968 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box 87, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1967–1968 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box 87, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1969–1970 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 87, Folder 4, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1969–1970 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 88, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1971–1972 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 88, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1971–1972 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 88, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1973–1974 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 88, Folder 4, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1973–1974 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 89, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1975–1978 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box 89, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1975–1978 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box 89, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1975–1978 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box 89, Folder 4, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, 1975–1978 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box 89, Folder 5, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1979–1981 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box 90, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1979–1981 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box 90, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1979–1981 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box 90, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1982–1983 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 90, Folder 4, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1982–1983 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 91, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1984–1985 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 91, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1984–1985 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 91, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Cashbook, receipts and disbursements, 1986 (Oversize-box 92, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - DGF Balance Sheet (From Irwin Bloom materials), 1992 Dec 31 (Oversize-box 92, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1992 June–1993 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 92, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1992 June–1993 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 92, Folder 4, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1994 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 92, Folder 5, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1994 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 93, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1995 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 93, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1995 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 93, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1996 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 93, Folder 4, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1996 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 94, Folder 1, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1998 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 94, Folder 2, Box 85)
  - General Ledger, 1998 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 94, Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Summary of account activity for Duke Gardens Foundation, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Summary of account activity for Duke Gardens Foundation, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Summary of account activity for Duke Gardens Foundation, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Summary of account activity for Duke Gardens Foundation, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Photographs/Slides, 1956-2001 and undated (Box 123)
  The over 2,300 miscellaneous color slides include images of the gardens (from different years), construction of Duke Gardens, individual plants, aerial views of gardens, views to outside areas such as entrances, and views of the grounds. These slides include duplicates that were made for Miss Duke. Of particular interest are the Pana-vue travel slides of Duke Gardens, commercially sold as souvenirs.
  The photographs are both in color and black and white, and in general document repairs and reconstruction to the different display gardens and grounds renovations.
  The images are loosely in chronological order and then alphabetically thereunder.
  - Color Slides of Gardens - Grounds-Outdoors, Preliminary Stages, Flowers, 1958-1959, 1964-1972 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - Succulent, Desert, Chinese, Moon Gate, Bamboo Room, and Japan, 1960-1969 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - Japan (continued), Indo-Persia, Tropical, and Semi-Tropical, 1960-1969 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (1 of 25) (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (2 of 25) (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (3 of 25) (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (4 of 25) (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (5 of 25) (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (6 of 25) (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (7 of 25) (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (8 of 25) (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (9 of 25) (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (10 of 25) (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (11 of 25) (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (12 of 25) (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (13 of 25) (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (14 of 25) (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (15 of 25) (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (16 of 25) (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (17 of 25) (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (18 of 25) (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1960, 1972-1977 (19 of 25) (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (20 of 25) (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (21 of 25) (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (22 of 25) (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (23 of 25) (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (24 of 25) (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - miscellaneous, 1960-1969, 1972-1977 (25 of 25) (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Color Slides of Gardens - Foyer, Italian, Colonial, Edwardian, French, Rock, and Herbaceous, 1961-1969 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Slides of China garden, 1965-1967 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Slides of Colonial garden, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Slides of Edwardian garden, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Slides of English garden, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Slides of Indo-Persia garden, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Slides of interior gardens, 1965-1967 (1 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Slides of interior gardens, 1965-1967 (2 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Slides of Italian garden, 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Slides of Japan garden, 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Slides of Semi Tropical garden, 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - English garden slides, March 1966 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Slides of interior gardens, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Photographs relating to Raritan Water Power Company repairs to canal, black and white, and captions, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of gardens and greenhouse construction, black and white, 12 January 1962 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of interior gardens including contstruction, planting and growing, black and white and color, 1963-1964 and undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Duke Gardens grounds and gardens, black and white, 15 June 1964 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of interior gardens, black and white, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of botanicals and gardens, color, March-April 1965 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of flood aftermath, black and white, 2 August 1965 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of gardens, January 1966 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of gardens and grounds, black and white, April 1966 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of interior gardens, color, June 1966 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Duke Gardens main gate, black and white, 27 August 1967 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous botanical and landscape photographs, location unknown, June 1971 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Viewmaster - Duke Gardens, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Color photographs - inventory/inventory cards, 1974-2000 (1 of 4) (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Color photographs - inventory/inventory cards, 1974-2000 (2 of 4) (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Color photographs - inventory/inventory cards, 1974-2000 (3 of 4) (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Color photographs - inventory/inventory cards, 1974-2000 (4 of 4) (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (1 of 8) (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (2 of 8) (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (3 of 8) (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (4 of 8) (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (5 of 8) (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (6 of 8) (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (7 of 8) (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstruction, 1996-1997 (8 of 8) (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Color photographs - Admin Building repairs and reconstruction, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Color photographs -vans, circa 1990s (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Color photographs - Bonsai collection, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Color photographs - landscape refurbishing, Sunken Fountain, Italy, Admin, 2000 Aug (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Color photographs - OR [Orchid Range] reconstruction/Grounds renovation, 2000 Sep (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstructions, 2001 (1 of 4) (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstructions, 2001 (2 of 4) (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstructions, 2001 (3 of 4) (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Color photographs - repairs and reconstructions, 2001 (4 of 4) (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Color panoramic photographs of Duke Gardens, undated (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Color photograph - flower 'White Dream', undated (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of grounds and equipment, black and white and color, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Park photographs, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of interior gardens, black and white, and photographic proof, aerial view of Duke Gardens greenhouses, color, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, presumably of visitors to Duke Gardens, black and white, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of visitors to Duke Gardens, black and white, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Legal Records, 1958-1999 (Box 106)
  The largest part of this series is the litigation between Duke Gardens Foundation and Universal Restoration Inc., a firm that was hired by the Duke Gardens Foundation to restore a few of the indoor display gardens. Materials include depositions from various witnesses including Doris Duke, exhibit materials, legal correspondence, construction and repair records, and architectural drawings. Other topics in this series include various insurance letters/certificates for the Duke Gardens Foundation, contracts for restoration and repairs at Duke Gardens, and general legal correspondence from various administrators at Duke Gardens Foundation.
  The records are in arranged in chronological order and alphabetically thereunder.
  RESTRICTED: Access to several folders in boxes 115, 117, and 119 are restricted and require prior written approval from the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation to view.
  - Contracts - Ernst Lundgren, 1958-1959 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correpondence from the office of J. Eaton, 1958-1959 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Richard Tongg, 1959-1960 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - construction and repair records, 1959-1970 (1 of 2) (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - construction and repair records, 1959-1970 (2 of 2) (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Insurances, 1959-1961 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Lord & Burnham invoices, 1960-1961 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Lord & Burnham correspondence, 1961 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Lord & Burnham invoices, 1961 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Lord & Burnham invoices, 1961-1966 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence regarding damage to lampost, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous insurance policies, 1962-1973 (1 of 2) (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous insurance policies, 1962-1973 (2 of 2) (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Edward Tirella, 1963-1966 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Deed to foundation (confirmatory), 1964 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous insurance policies, 1964-1970 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Survey maps of Duke Gardens Foundation. Includes copy of indenture for establishment of DGF, 1964-1970 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Certificates of insurance, 1965-1993 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence regarding unauthorized photos of Duke Gardens, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, 1966-1998 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - reports on conditions of Gardens, 1967-1969 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Defendant's exhibits, 1968-1970 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Comstock letters to Universal, 1969-1970 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - miscellaneous correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Doris Duke, 1970 Jun 25 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Darryl G. Copeland, Lillian E. Emerson, Basil Hanger, 1970 Jul 16 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Allyn Eric Kilsheimer, Kenneth S. Eisenberg, Clarence Eldridge Williams Jr., 1970 Sep 14 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Clarence Eldridge Williams, 1970 Sep 15 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Clarence Eldridge Williams, Jr., 1970 Sep 28 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Clarence Eldridge Williams, Jr., Allyn Eric Kilsheimer, 1970 Sep 29 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Kenneth S. Eisenberg, 1970 Sep 30 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - DGF vs. Universal Restoration, Inc. - Deposition upon oral examination of Patti Gamache, Kenneth S. Eisenberg, 1970 Oct 22 (Box 110, Folder 6)